[{
	"question":"Q. What type of keys are ctrl and shift?",
	"options" : [ "adjustment", "function", "modifier", "alphanumeric" ],
	"answer" : "modifier"
},
{
	"question":"Q. In Word, replace option is a available on -",
	"options" : [ "File Menu", "View Menu", "Edit Menu", "Format Menu" ],
	"answer" : "Edit Menu"
},
{
	"question":"The binary system is a number system to the base -",
	"options" : [ "2", "4", "8", "10" ],
	"answer" : "4"
},
{
	"question":"Q. Which of the following is not an example of hardware?",
	"options" : [ "Scanner", "Printer", "Monitor", "Interpreter" ],
	"answer" : "Interpreter"
},
{
	"question":"Q. In excel, this is a pre-recorded formula that provides a shortcut for complex calculations -",
	"options" : [ "Value", "Data Series", "Function", "Field" ],
	"answer" : "Function"
},
{ 
  "question": "Q. This is not a function category in Excel -",
  "answer": "Data Series",
  "options": [ "Logical", "Data Series", "Financial", "Text" ] 
},
{ 
  "question": "Q. This is not a function category in Excel -",
  "answer": "Data Series",
  "options": [ "Logical", "Data Series", "Financial", "Text" ] 
},
{ "question": "Q. On a CD-RW you can",
  "answer": "read, write and rewrite information",
  "options":
   [ "read and write information.",
     "only read information.",
     "only write information.",
     "read, write and rewrite information" ] 
},
{ 
  "question": "Q. To be able to 'boot', the computer must have a(n)",
  "answer": "Operating system",
  "options": [ "Compiler", "Loader", "Operating system", "Assembler" ] 
},
{ "question": "Q. The operating system that is self-contained in a device and resident in the ROM is -",
  "answer": "Embedded Operating System",
  "options":
   [ "Batch Operating System",
     "Real-time Operating System",
     "Embedded Operating System",
     "Multi-Processor Operating System" ] 
},
{ "question": "Q. To make a copy of the current document on the disk -",
  "answer": "Use the 'save as' command",
  "options":
   [ "Use the 'save' command",
     "This cannot be done",
     "Use the 'duplicate' command",
     "Use the 'save as' command" ] 
}]